GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING
On the 3rd of April 2014, while ministering at The South Korea Pastors' Conference,
Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a prophecy concerning a vision God had given him about North and South Korea.
Here are his words...
In your country here, whatever threat you are having now is not a threat.
You people will still come to the table to talk reconciliation between you people and North.
There is no fight between South and North.
Whatever threat now, they will still come together and discuss.
They will not fight but there will be threat, threat, threat.
There will be threat, threat, threat - gunshot threat - but you people will still discuss.
There will be reconciliation.
I am seeing reconciliation coming. Discussion will come.
South Korea Pastors' Conference
With Prophet T.B. Joshua